

Marcos Vila Obarrio

Fullstack Developer | Business Manager

Hello, my name is Marcos. I am 26 years old. I graduated in Business Administration and worked in the finance area for 5 years. My last experience was at Price Waterhouse Coopers. During that process, I learned to work in a team, adapt and be reliable. Today, I want to learn from a good boss in the world of web/app development.

Contact Info

+541155252721

marcosvila96@gmail.com

bit.ly/marcosvilaobarrio

Education

soyHENRY

2022

Universidad Catolica Argentina

2016 - 2021

San Juan El Precursor High School

2001 - 2014

Hard Skills

Front End Development

React.js | HTML5 | CSS | Redux

Back End Development

Express | Node.js | MySQL

Soft Skills

Reliable | Focus | Teamwork | Funny

Work Experience

Tax Specialist - Price Waterhouse Coopers jan 2021 - dec 2021

Management of accounting balances.

Data entry to the database.

Remote meetings with foreign accountants.

English classes

Financial Advisor - Coswell

feb 2020 - nov 2020

Complete risk analyses.

Contact client to report about news and portfolio.

Year planning for investment solutions.

Commercial Assistant - MAKRO

mar 2019 - nov 2019

Price lists, excel management and email.

Negotiation with suppliers. Stock maintenance.

For More Information



This Barcode Redirect to My Personal Website bit.ly/marcosvilaobarrio